<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="low_memory" product="shield">SHIELD storage is full. Delete some files to free space.</string>
    <string name="power_dialog" product="shield">SHIELD options</string>
    <string name="shutdown_confirm" product="shield">SHIELD will shut down.</string>
    <string name="global_actions" product="shield">SHIELD options</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSms" product="shield">Allows the app to read SMS
      messages stored on your SHIELD or SIM card. This allows the app to read all
      SMS messages, regardless of content or confidentiality.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSms" product="shield">Allows the app to write
      to SMS messages stored on your SHIELD or SIM card. Malicious apps
      may delete your messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_injectEvents" product="shield">Allows the app to deliver
        its own input events (key presses, etc.) to other apps. Malicious
        apps may use this to take over SHIELD.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_persistentActivity" product="shield">Allows the app to make parts of itself persistent in memory.  This can limit memory available to other apps and slow down SHIELD.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_clearAppCache" product="shield">Allows the app to free SHIELD storage
        by deleting files in the cache directories of other apps.  This may cause other
        apps to start up more slowly as they need to re-retrieve their data.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readLogs" product="shield">Allows the app to read from the
        system\'s various log files.  This allows it to discover general
        information about what you are doing with SHIELD, potentially
        including personal or private information.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeComponentState" product="shield">Allows the app to change whether a
        component of another app is enabled or not. Malicious apps may use this
        to disable important SHIELD capabilities. Care must be used with this permission, as it is
        possible to get app components into an unusable, inconsistent, or unstable state.
    </string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveBootCompleted" product="shield">Allows the app to
        have itself started as soon as the system has finished booting.
        This can make it take longer to start SHIELD and allow the
        app to slow down overall SHIELD performance by always running.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastSticky" product="shield">Allows the app to
    send sticky broadcasts, which remain after the broadcast ends. Excessive use
    may make SHIELD slow or unstable by causing it to use too much memory.
    </string>
    <string name="permdesc_readContacts" product="shield">Allows the app to read
      data about your contacts stored on SHIELD, including the frequency
      with which you\'ve called, emailed, or communicated in other ways with
      specific individuals. This permission allows apps to save your contact
      data, and malicious apps may share contact data without your
      knowledge.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeContacts" product="shield">Allows the app to
      modify the data about your contacts stored on your SHIELD, including the
      frequency with which you\'ve called, emailed, or communicated in other ways
      with specific contacts. This permission allows apps to delete contact
      data.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCallLog" product="shield">Allows the app to read
     SHIELD\'s call log, including data about incoming and outgoing calls.
     This permission allows apps to save your call log data, and malicious apps
     may share call log data without your knowledge.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeCallLog" product="shield">Allows the app to modify SHIELD\'s call log, including data about incoming and outgoing calls.
        Malicious apps may use this to erase or modify your call log.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCalendar" product="shield">Allows the app to read
       all calendar events stored on your SHIELD, including those of friends or
       co-workers. This may allow the app to share or save your calendar data,
       regardless of confidentiality or sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeCalendar" product="shield">Allows the app to
     add, remove, and change events that you can modify on your SHIELD, including
     those of friends or co-workers. This may allow the app to send messages
     that appear to come from calendar owners, or modify events without the
     owners\' knowledge.</string>
    <string name="permlab_brick" product="shield">permanently disable SHIELD</string>
    <string name="permdesc_brick" product="shield">Allows the app to
        permanently disable SHIELD. This is very dangerous.</string>
    <string name="permlab_reboot" product="shield">force SHIELD reboot</string>
    <string name="permdesc_reboot" product="shield">Allows the app to force SHIELD to reboot.</string>
    <string name="permlab_performCdmaProvisioning" product="shield">directly start CDMA SHIELD setup</string>
    <string name="permlab_wakeLock" product="shield">prevent SHIELD from sleeping</string>
    <string name="permdesc_wakeLock" product="shield">Allows the app to prevent SHIELD from going to sleep.</string>
    <string name="permlab_devicePower" product="shield">power SHIELD on or off</string>
    <string name="permdesc_devicePower" product="shield">Allows the app to turn
        SHIELD on or off.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_factoryTest" product="shield">Run as a low-level manufacturer test,
        allowing complete access to SHIELD hardware. Only available
        when SHIELD is running in manufacturer test mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTime" product="shield">Allows the app to change SHIELD\'s clock time.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTimeZone" product="shield">Allows the app to change SHIELD\'s time zone.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getAccounts" product="shield">Allows the app to get
      the list of accounts known by SHIELD.  This may include any accounts
      created by applications you have installed.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWifiMulticastState" product="shield">Allows the app to receive
      packets sent to all devices on a Wi-Fi network using multicast addresses,
      not just your SHIELD.  It uses more power than the non-multicast mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetoothAdmin" product="shield">Allows the app to
      configure the local Bluetooth SHIELD, and to discover and pair with remote
      devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWimaxState" product="shield">Allows the app to
      connect SHIELD to and disconnect SHIELD from WiMAX networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetooth" product="shield">Allows the app to view the
      configuration of Bluetooth on SHIELD, and to make and accept
      connections with paired devices.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_watchLogin" product="shield">Monitor the number of incorrect passwords
    typed when unlocking the screen, and lock SHIELD or erase all SHIELD\'s
    data if too many incorrect passwords are typed.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_wipeData" product="shield">Erase SHIELD\'s data without warning by performing a factory data reset.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_missing_sim_message" product="shield">No SIM card in SHIELD.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_glogin" product="shield">
        You have incorrectly drawn your unlock pattern <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       After <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> more unsuccessful attempts,
       you will be asked to unlock your SHIELD using your Google signin.\n\n
       Try again in <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> seconds.
    </string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_at_wipe" product="shield">
       You have incorrectly attempted to unlock SHIELD <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       After <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> more unsuccessful attempts,
       SHIELD will be reset to the factory default and all user data will be lost.
    </string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_now_wiping" product="shield">
       You have incorrectly attempted to unlock SHIELD <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       SHIELD will now be reset to the factory default.
    </string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeHistoryBookmarks" product="shield">Allows the
        app to modify the browser\'s history or bookmarks stored on SHIELD.
        This may allow the app to erase or modify browser data.  Note: this
        permission may not be enforced by third-party browsers or other
        applications with web-browsing capabilities.</string>
    <string name="enable_explore_by_touch_warning_message" product="shield"><xliff:g id="accessibility_service_name">%1$s</xliff:g> wants to enable Explore by Touch.
            When Explore by Touch is turned on, you can hear or see descriptions of what\'s under
            your finger or perform gestures to interact with SHIELD.</string>
    <string name="default_audio_route_name" product="shield">SHIELD</string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_almost_at_wipe" product="shield">
       You have incorrectly attempted to unlock SHIELD <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       After <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> more unsuccessful attempts,
       SHIELD will be reset to the factory default and all user data will be lost.
    </string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_now_wiping" product="shield">
       You have incorrectly attempted to unlock SHIELD <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       SHIELD will now be reset to the factory default.
    </string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_almost_at_login" product="shield">
       You have incorrectly drawn your unlock pattern <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> times.
       After <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> more unsuccessful attempts,
       you will be asked to unlock your SHIELD using an email account.\n\n
       Try again in <xliff:g id="number">%d</xliff:g> seconds.
    </string>
    <string name="permdesc_transmitIr" product="shield">Allows the app to use SHIELD\'s infrared transmitter.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetoothPriv" product="shield">Allows the app to pair with remote devices without user interaction.</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_frequency_conflict_message" product="shield">
      SHIELD will temporarily disconnect from Wi-Fi while it\'s connected to %1$s
    </string>
</resources>
